const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "Leeds, United Kingdom is the birthplace of what Borussen?",
    answers: ["Marwin Hitz", "Jadon Sancho", "Manuel Akanji", "Erling Braut Håland"],
    correct: "Erling Braut Håland",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
      'Paco Alcácer was born in',
    answers: ["Petra, Spain", "Braga, Portugal", "Torrent, Spain", "Madrid, Spain"],
    correct: "Torrent, Spain",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "With 127 goals, this player is 7th on Dortmund's all-time top 10 goalscorers",
    answers: ["Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang", "Marco Reus", "Jürgen Schütz", "Lothar Emmerich"],
    correct: "Marco Reus",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question: "Nuri Sahin became the Bundesliga's youngest scorer at what age?",
    answers: [
      "16 years & 238 days",
      "17 years & 82 days",
      "16 years & 334 days",
      "17 years & 37 days"
    ],
    correct: "17 years & 82 days",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the Westfalenstadion open?",
    answers: [
      "1972",
      "1978",
      "1974",
      "1975"
    ],
    correct: "1974",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question: "Ewerthon scored the goal to give Borussia Dortmund the lead over Bremen after only being on for _____.",
  answers: [
    "1 minute 4 seconds",
    "49 seconds",
    "1 minute 23 seconds",
    "38 seconds"
  ],
  correct: "49 seconds",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question: "Borussia Dortmund finished at the top of the table with ____ in the 11/12 season.",
  answers: [
    "81 points",
    "75 points",
    "78 points",
    "80 points"
  ],
  correct: "81 points",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question: "Cruising to a 4-1 victory, beating which team in the final of the 1988-89 DFB-Pokal?",
    answers: ["VfB Stuttgart", "FC Bayern", "Werder Bremen", "Bayer 04"],
    correct: "Werder Bremen",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many years did Borussia Dortmund get their first win against Sch*lke?",
    answers: ["18", "3", "7", "23"],
    correct: "18",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
      "With 10 goals this player is the top time scorer in the Revierderby?",
    answers: [
      "Ingo Anderbrügge",
      "Michael Zorc",
      "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang",
      "Lothar Emmerich"
    ],
    correct: "Lothar Emmerich",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player is a noted Dragon Ball fan?",
    answers: ["Hakimi", "Zaga", "Sancho", "Dahoud"],
    correct: "Zaga",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: "This player is red-green colorblind?",
    answers: ["Julian Brandt", "Roman Bürki", "Thomas Delaney", "Marco Reus"],
    correct: "Thomas Delaney",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was not apart of the 10/11 champion team",
    answers: ["Ilkay Gündogan", "Lukasz Piszczek", "Mario Götze", "Mitchell Langerak"],
    correct: "Ilkay Gündogan",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was not in the 94/95 champion team?",
    answers: ["Andreas Möller", "Stefan Klos", "Matthias Sammer", "Marco Kurz"],
    correct: "Marco Kurz",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: "Lucien Favre was born in",
    answers: ["Wiesendangen, Switzerland", "Saint-Barthelemy, Switzerland", "Münsingen, Switzerland", "St. Gallen, Switzerland"],
    correct: "Skin",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: "Lucien Favre became the first ever manager to remain unbeaten for how many Bundesliga matches",
    answers: ["10", "20", "15", "18"],
    correct: "15",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capacity of the Westfalenstadion?",
    answers: ["81365", "81455", "81220", "81565"],
    correct: "81365",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Borussia Dortmund returned to the Bundesliga in?",
    answers: ["1973", "1975", "1976", "1978"],
    correct: "1976",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which company has not been a supplier of Dortmund kits?",
    answers: ["Adidas", "Nike", "Kappa", "Umbro"],
    correct: "Umbro",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: "Błaszczykowski was plagued by a torn leg muscle in which season?",
    answers: [
      "2008-09",
      "2009-10",
      "2010-11",
      "2012-13"
    ],
    correct: "2008-09",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: "On 1 August 2016 Błaszczykowski joined Wolfsburg for?",
    answers: ["€4 million ", "€8 million", "€5 million", "€12 million"],
    correct: "€5 million",
    questionId: "2019778"
  },
  {
    question: "Shinji Kagawa initially joined Borussia Dortmund for?",
    answers: ["€3.5 million", "€350,000", "€700,000", "€5 million"],
    correct: "€350,000",
    questionId: "2134343"
  },
  {
    question: "Christian Pulisic joined Chelsea in 2019 for a fee of?",
    answers: [
      "€64 million",
      "€50 million",
      "€46 million",
      "€75 million"
    ],
    correct: "€64 million",
    questionId: "2210799"
  },
  {
    question:
      "When is Marco Reus' birthday?",
    answers: ["October 31", "July 6", "February 29", "May 31"],
    correct: "May 31",
    questionId: "2379831"
  },
  {
    question: "Which manager signed Guerreiro?",
    answers: ["Tuchel", "Stöger", "Favre", "Bosz"],
    correct: "Tuchel",
    questionId: "2426418"
  },
  {
    question: "How fast did Erling Håland score a hattrick on his debut?",
    answers: ["45 minutes", "23 minutes", "36 minutes", "12 minutes"],
    correct: "23 minutes",
    questionId: "2510086"
  }
];

export default (n = 1) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
